Let's go, Master.
لنذهب يا معلمة.
Those bandits
أولئك اللصوص
can't stay either.
لا يمكن البقاء أيضا.
Ah.
آه.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Watch out!
احترس!
Master
يتقن
Cheng Dalei,
تشنغ دالي ،
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
Black Rock City and Green Bull Mountain will form an alliance,
ستشكل مدينة بلاك روك سيتي وجرين بول ماونتين تحالفًا ،
Heroes don't ask where they came from.
لا يسأل الأبطال من أين أتوا.
I believe you are a man.
أعتقد أنك رجل.
I'll leave the people of Black Rock to you.
سأترك شعب بلاك روك لك.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
-دعنا نذهب.  -دعنا نذهب.
I dare not forget to worry about my country,
لا أجرؤ على أن أنسى القلق على بلدي ،
why should I ask about cloth and silks when I am exiled?
لماذا أسأل عن القماش والحرير وأنا منفى؟
Come on.
تعال.
I'm going to avenge my son today.
سأنتقم لابني اليوم.
No
لا
Yellow missions are so dangerous.
المهمات الصفراء خطيرة للغاية.
The red mission,
المهمة الحمراء ،
Master,
يتقن،
Let's go back.
دعنا نعود.
The Rong invasion only robs the city people,
غزو ​​رونغ سلب سكان المدينة فقط ،
while we in Qingniu Mountain are in the backcountry,
بينما نحن في جبل تشينغنيو في المناطق النائية ،
They won't come.
لن يأتوا.
With the Tiger Tally,
مع Tiger Tally ،
I can open the gate.
يمكنني فتح البوابة.
To lure the Rong Clan into the Pass,
لجذب Rong Clan إلى الممر ،
and make a big plan together,
ووضع خطة كبيرة معًا ،
I dare not forget to worry about the country,
لا أجرؤ على أن أنسى القلق على البلد ،
so I'll leave the people of Black Rock City to you
لذلك سأترك سكان بلاك روك سيتي لكم
if they drive away the Lu Clan and ask for cloth and silks.
إذا دفعوا بعيدًا عن Lu Clan وطلبوا القماش والحرير.
I've decided not to go back to Toad Village.
قررت عدم العودة إلى قرية العلجوم.
I'm going to Black Rock City.
انا ذاهب الى بلاك روك سيتي.
Master,
يتقن،
Black Rock City,
بلاك روك سيتي ،
You're going to die.
انت ستموت.
When I first came to Toad Village,
عندما أتيت لأول مرة إلى قرية العلجوم ،
I didn't want to be the Head of the Fortress at all.
لم أكن أريد أن أكون رئيس القلعة على الإطلاق.
I was forced to do all of this.
اضطررت للقيام بكل هذا.
But since I met you,
لكن منذ أن قابلتك ،
I realized,
أدركت،
I'm not alone.
أنا لست وحيدا.
I have a partner
لدي شريك
and a family.
وعائلة.
With someone I'm worth caring about,
مع شخص ما أستحق الاهتمام به ،
now in Qingniu Mountain,
الآن في جبل تشينغنيو ،
That's my home.
هذا منزلي.
But now,
لكن الآن،
I understand a truth better,
أنا أفهم الحقيقة بشكل أفضل ،
Even though there are countless small families in the world,
على الرغم من وجود عدد لا يحصى من العائلات الصغيرة في العالم ،
but Black Rock City,
لكن مدينة بلاك روك
Falling Leaf City,
مدينة Falling Leaf ،
and even Youzhou,
وحتى Youzhou ،
It's also the people of thousands of people.
إنه أيضًا شعب الآلاف من الناس.
Friends of Toad Village,
أصدقاء قرية العلجوم ،
would you like to join me?
هل تود مرافقتي؟
Protect the happiness of millions of people.
حماية سعادة الملايين من الناس.
Qin Man is willing
تشين مان على استعداد
to accompany you,
لمرافقتك ،
To the end of the world.
الى نهاية العالم.
Canghai Lin Shaoyu.
كانغهاي لين شاويو.
I'm willing to stay with you
أنا على استعداد للبقاء معك
for the rest of my life.
لبقية حياتي.
I appreciate your passion,
أنا أقدر شغفك ،
but you're still young,
لكنك ما زلت صغيرا
But I didn't know it was a dangerous journey,
لكن لم أكن أعلم أنها كانت رحلة خطيرة ،
that Black Rock City,
مدينة بلاك روك تلك ،
How can you come in whenever you want?
كيف يمكنك الدخول وقتما تشاء؟
You can come up with a place you want.
يمكنك الخروج بالمكان الذي تريده.
That is, the Grand Advisor of Toad Village,
أي ، المستشار الأكبر لقرية العلجوم ،
who will help you with your advice.
من سيساعدك بنصائحك.
There's still a chance.
لا تزال هناك فرصة.
I, the jade-faced scholar Xu Shenji,
أنا ، الباحث ذو الوجه اليشم Xu Shenji ،
am willing to go to Black Rock City
أنا على استعداد للذهاب إلى مدينة بلاك روك
with Master.
مع ماجستير.
Oh my goodness,
يا إلهي،